{
    "subject": "resource/Girlfriend_(B2K_song)",
    "predicate": "ontology/recordLabel",
    "object": "resource/Epic_Records",
    "human_readable": "The song 'Girlfriend' by B2K was released under Epic Records.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.5482602119445801,
            "question": "Which record label released 'Girlfriend'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38707271218299866,
            "question": "Who is the artist behind the song 'Girlfriend'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3481493294239044,
            "question": "What year was 'Girlfriend' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3139178454875946,
            "question": "Is 'Girlfriend' a popular song?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.297776997089386,
            "question": "What genre of music is 'Girlfriend'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28374990820884705,
            "question": "What is the general theme of the song 'Girlfriend'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24521952867507935,
            "question": "Is there a music video for 'Girlfriend'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11465062201023102,
            "question": "Are there any notable remixes or covers of 'Girlfriend'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10353082418441772,
            "question": "Did 'Girlfriend' achieve commercial success?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09159685671329498,
            "question": "Has 'Girlfriend' been featured in any movies or TV shows?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The song 'Girlfriend' by B2K was released under Epic Records.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2495_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did 'Girlfriend' achieve commercial success?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2495_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable remixes or covers of 'Girlfriend'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2495_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a music video for 'Girlfriend'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2495_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2495_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2495_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2495_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2495_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2495_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2495_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2495_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2495_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2495_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2495_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The information provided in the documents supports the statement that the song 'Girlfriend' by B2K was released under Epic Records. This can be inferred from the document with file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2495/re-ranker-msmarco/83.txt, which lists \"Epic Records\" as the label for the \"Girlfriend\" single by B2K."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}